(Sheldon:)an outward appearance of acceptance.
(Mrs Cooper:)That is very Christian of you.
(Sheldon:)Mother, if you're going
to conduct your life in this fashion,
(Sheldon:)then I should let you know
that the world has changed
(Sheldon:)since you were a young woman.
(Sheldon:)You know, it's not all sock hops,
soda jerks and segregation anymore.
(Mrs Cooper:)How old do you think I am?
(Sheldon:)My point is that you're going
to need to be careful.
(Sheldon:)You used to be protected by your
pre-Enlightenment mythology,
(Sheldon:)but now you're going
to need a stronger friend
(Sheldon:)named latex.
(Mrs Cooper:)Are you having the sex talk with me?
(Sheldon:)Well, someone has to.
Oh, dear Lord!
(Sheldon:)No, don't look to Him.
He's mad at you right now.
(Penny:)Come on, don't pout.
I'm sorry I ruined your game.